ukvapers.org 2016-06-07

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**   

Privacy Policy  
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to UK Vapers. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used.

Registration  
Some basic personal information is required in order to register with UK Vapers:

Email Address - By providing your email address, you can receive important messages via your existing email account. Forum notifications rely on the email address you provide when you register.

User Name - This is how you are identified when you participate in forums. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed except by request to UK Vapers Management

Date of Birth - this essential for us to ensure we only have adult (over 18 years) members of UK Vapers

Location – this is so other members know where in the world you live (particularly useful when using the classified sales sections) and can be as broad as a country or as narrow as a town. Do not provide your full address in this field!

When you register, and subsequently as a member, you are given the option of providing, in your member's profile, other demographic information (like occupation, gender, etc). This can be helpful to other members who wish to communicate with you.

Protection of Children's Online Privacy  
No-one under 18 is allowed to participate in UK Vapers

Cookies  
The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join UK Vapers, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that UK Vapers obtains this information when you login to your UK Vapers account and use the forum. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on UK Vapers to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, UK Vapers checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the UK Vapers login screen, where you can login to your account, or register an account if you are not a member. Cookies are also used to check to ensure that you have permission to access or post in particular UK Vapers sub-forums. UK Vapers do not divulge these cookies to anyone else. 

When you first connect to UK Vapers, most browser will display a banner informing you of the use of Cookies by UK Vapers and asking you to agree to this. If you choose not to agree, your use of UK Vapers will be severely limited.

UK Vapers neither use nor permit cookies from third parties. The only exception to this are Cookies used by Google Analytics, which UK Vapers use in an anonymised form for general analysis of forum use. Members not wishing to have Google Analytics applied to their use of the forum (anonymised) should visit this link and follow the instructions provided: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Forums  
UK Vapers hosts message boards, chat and other services. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public forums becomes public information. In addition, information that is disclosed in private forums may be disclosed by other forum participants. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

IP Address  
In common with most sites on the Internet, every time you log into or post on UK Vapers, the forum software records your current [IP Address](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address). This is done to protect the site from abuse. We will not disclose this IP Address to anyone except where required by law

Security  
UK Vapers' site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. UK Vapers' servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can contact us via the [Contact Us](http://ukvapers.org/Forum-Contact-Us) Forum, or by email to info@ukvapers.org 

* * *

Massive thanks to everyone who helped my daughter and me raise over £500 for Macmillan Cancer Support through our OutRun May Challenge 

(This post was last modified: 03/11/13 09:36 PM by [Phil A](http://ukvapers.org/User-Phil-A). )
